《指定幸存者》前情提要
"Designated Survivor"...
-马吉德·纳萨尔死了  -说他被投毒
- Majid Nassar is dead? - They say he was poisoned.
纳萨尔与袭击的关联
Peter MacLeish has closer ties to the attack
远不及彼得·麦克利什  而且我们有证据
than Nassar ever did, and we have evidence of that.
柯克曼得知道这一点
Kirkman needs to know that.
我们再也找不到一个比麦克利什
We're never gonna find a better candidate
更适合副总统一职的候选人了
for Vice President than MacLeish.
希望你已经查出结果了
Please tell me that you've got some answers.
我们会调查一切可能性
We're looking into every possibility.
我以为不用再应付这事了
I never thought I'd be dealing with this again --
无论李奥是不是我的亲生儿子
whether or not Leo was mine.
卡特兰是个雇佣兵  也是一个叛国者
Catalan's a mercenary and a traitor.
我知道是谁杀了纳萨尔
I know who killed Nassar.
只要你照我说的去做  你的儿子就会没事的
Your son will be safe as long as you do everything I tell you to do.
跟总统预约会面
Make an appointment with the President.
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
这是马吉德·纳萨尔的葬礼
This is the Janazah of Majid Nassar.
今天是2月6日
The date is February 6th.
现在时间是21点8分
The time is 21:08.
明天将是我国历史上的一个重要时刻
Tomorrow marks a momentous occasion in our nation's history.
将是一场史无前例的选举
It's an unprecedented election
国会选举
将选出一个新的众议院
to choose a new House of Representatives.
国会选举
这也是在国会大厦袭击案之后
It is also the next, and perhaps most important step,
柯特曼总统将采取的下一步政府重建计划
President Kirkman is taking to re-establish our government
也许是最重要的一步
in the wake of the Capitol attack.
白宫
总统呼吁每一位美国民众
The President urges every American,
无论其政治立场是什么
no matter what their political affiliation,
明天都来投票
get out there tomorrow and cast a vote.
娜塔莉
Yeah, Natalie.
赛斯  白宫是否在关注
Seth, is the White House concerned
一种新型的H5N1超级流感病毒
about a new strain of the H5N1 super-flu?
在过去二十四小时内
12 reported cases in the Kansas City area
堪萨斯城已经发现十二例病例
in the last 24 hours,
所有的已知的抗体...
all resistant to known treatment --
目前疾控中心已经着手了
Yeah, so far the CDC's been tracking that,
不必惊慌  好吗
and there's no cause for alarm, okay?
如果没有问题了
If there are no further questions,
感谢大家出席下一场简报
thank you all for very much for another exciting briefing.
赛斯  马吉德·纳萨尔是不是已经死了
Seth, is Majid Nassar dead?
-亚伦  -我知道了
- Aaron. - I know.
我收到布拉格堡的消息
I have a source at Fort Bragg,
据称一名穆斯林教士
says a Muslim chaplain
于昨天下午六点上了飞机
was put on a plane yesterday at 6:00 P.M.
被告知去为一个穆斯林葬礼做准备
Told to prepare for a Muslim burial.
第二条消息证实葬礼是为了一名重要的囚犯
A second source confirms it was for a high-value prisoner,
几乎可以肯定是马吉德·纳萨尔
almost certainly Majid Nassar.
没错
Yes, that's true.
两天前  马吉德·纳萨尔被发现死在狱中
Two days ago, Majid Nassar was found dead in his jail cell.
他被逮捕  拘留以及审问的情况
The circumstances of his capture, detention, and interrogation
都涉及国家安全  我没有...
are all matters of national security, and I have no --
赛斯  他的死是不是因为加强审讯技术
Seth, is he dead because of enhanced interrogation techniques,
或者说是被拷打致死
or what some would call torture?
不是  犯人是严格按照《日内瓦公约》
No. The prisoner was kept in the strictest accordance
被拘禁的
with the Geneva Convention.
总统只允许这种方式
This President would have it no other way.
国会选举
不好意思  但这是目前我能告诉你的
I'm sorry, but that's really all I can tell you at this time, okay?
谢谢大家
Thank you guys.
-总统先生  -赛斯做得对
- Mr. President. - Seth did the right thing.
我们统一过意见的  如果事发就公布真相
We agreed. If it came up, we would go with the truth.
如果我们主动宣布此事的话会更好
I would have liked it if we could have announced it ourselves,
但我们还没有弄清真相
but we didn't have the facts.
不幸的是  这会让纳萨尔的死
Well, unfortunately, this is only gonna
引发更多的猜想
lead to more questions about Nassar's death.
还会影响你的形象  他们说他是被折磨致死
And your integrity. They're saying he died of torture.
-赛斯否认了  -恕我直言  总统先生
- Seth denied that. - With all due respect, Mr. President,
只说"不是"  而缺少具体细节
simply saying no lacks a certain specificity
媒体是不会接受的
that the press will not accept.
如果我们不马上处理此事
If we don't address this right away in detail,
这种言论会上头版头条
it'll dominate the headlines.
让我们的选举无人问津
It'll force the elections to take a back seat.
调查有什么进展吗
Where are we at with the investigation?
亚特伍德最终回电话了  他十点会到这里
Atwood finally called back. He'll be here at 10:00.
希望他这次能有点消息
Let's hope he's got something for us this time.
中情局报告
内斯特·洛萨诺
我欠你一顿大餐
I owe you a bear claw.
你整晚都在这里吗
You've been here all night?
你今天穿得跟昨天一样
You're wearing the same thing you wore yesterday.
那是谁  新线索吗
Who's that? A new lead?
只是一份我之前没读的目击者证词
Just a witness statement I never got around to reading.
杰森还没来上班吗
Hey, has Jason logged in to the system yet?
我还没看见他
I haven't seen him.
没错  他办公室也在找他
Yeah, his office is looking for him, too.
他没回短信也没回邮件
He's not answering texts or e-mails.
我以为只有你能知道他在哪了
I kind of figured if anyone knew where he was, it'd be you.
说曹操  曹操到
Speak of the devil.
杰森
Jason.
卢克还好吗  你找到他了吗
Is Luke okay? - Did you -- did you find him?
找到了  他...
Yeah, he was --
他在朋友家
He was at his friend's house.
我昨晚给你打了好多次电话
I called 10 times last night.
我知道  谢谢
I know. Thank you.
对不起  我没回你
I'm sorry I didn't get back to you.
我只是有点担心  我以为是...
I was just worried. I thought it might be...
阴谋吗  不不
Conspiracy? No, no.
幸好不是
Thank God it wasn't.
不  他...
No, he, um...
不在他应该在的地方
wasn't where he was supposed to be.
杰森  如果你需要  我可以帮忙
You know, Jason, if you ever need anything, I'm here to help.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要接吗
You gonna answer that?
是的  能先出去一下吗
Yeah, when you give me some privacy.
当然了
Of course.
威尔士探员  你想帮忙吗
Agent Wells, you want to help?
查一下威德尔案
Look into the Weddle case.
威德尔案  那个案子有什么关联吗
The Weddle case? What does that have to do with anything?
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好  -早上好  杰森
- Hello? - Good morning, Jason.
我...
Yeah, I, um...
-我安排了跟总统的见面  -非常好
- I set up the meeting with the President. - That's very good.
我们很感谢你没把我们谈话的事告诉别人
And we appreciate you not telling anyone about our conversation.
卢克也很感谢
Luke does, too.
我想现在跟我儿子通话
I want to speak to my son right now.
待在办公室  等我们的下一个电话
Stay in your office. Wait for our next call.
喂
Hello?
恰克
Hey, Chuck.
别声张  帮我个忙
Listen, keep this between us,
威德尔案的全部案件信息给我一份
but get me everything you can on the Weddle case.
为什么
Why?
现在还说不好
I don't know yet.
无意冒犯  总统先生
With all due respect, Mr. President,
作为国会唯二的成员之一
as half of Congress,
我不应该是从信息推送中收到纳萨尔的死讯
I shouldn't have to find out about Nassar's death on my RSS feed.
你说得对
You're absolutely right.
我知道  非常抱歉
And I know. And I am sorry.
只是我想完全确定之后再告诉你
I just didn't feel comfortable saying anything until we knew.
你真的不知道是谁杀了马吉德·纳萨尔吗
You really don't know who killed Majid Nassar?
也不知道手法和死因
Or how? Or why?
很遗憾  是的
Unfortunately, no.
但是我们已经在调查了
Obviously, the investigation is under way.
我向你保证  从现在开始
And I promise you, from now on,
我们会随时通知你和你的团队
we will keep you - and your office informed.
他分明被关在高度警戒的军事监狱中
The man was in a military prison under maximum security.
现在已经过了两天
Two days have gone by,
还没人能查清他是怎么死的
and no one can tell us how he managed to die?
我明白你的意思  情况很糟糕
I don't disagree with you. It's bad.
我知道我们之间有不少分歧
And I know that you and I have had our differences,
但是我们不能让这件事
but we cannot allow this one instance
影响到明天的重要选举
to overshadow the importance of tomorrow's elections.
这是第一步
This is the first step
是国家走向复兴之路的第一步
that we are taking - to rebuilding our country.
政府必须统一战线齐心协力
We need our government to work at full strength,
国会和议长必须携手并肩
and it cannot without its Congress and its Speaker.
我会尽全力帮你组建国会
I'll do everything I can to get you that Congress.
谢谢你
Thank you.
总统先生
Mr. President.
抱歉打扰  有急事
I'm sorry. This is an emergency.
是肯萨斯市的事情
It's about that situation in Kansas City.
这位是疾病控制中心的阿诺德医生
This is Dr. Arnold from the CDC,
以及陆军中校加茨  来自陆军医院
Lieutenant Colonel Gatz, Army Medical.
发生什么事
What's going on?
中西部地区爆发的流感...
That flu outbreak in the Midwest --
-经查明并不是流感  -那是什么
- It's not the flu, sir. - What is it?
情况要比流感严重得多  总统先生
I'm afraid it's far more serious, Mr. President.
症状显示应该是人造毒素
The infected are victims of a synthetic toxin.
-毒素  -是蓖麻毒素
- Toxin? - Ricin, sir.
存在形式是极细颗粒
In extreme-fine powder form.
天哪
My God.
这不是传染病  先生
It's not an epidemic, sir.
对  是生化恐怖袭击
No. It's an act of bioterrorism.
指定幸存者
第一季 第八集
翻译：   sienna  青椒  桃子  Silence
■
已确认的十二例病例  年龄不同
Each of the 12 confirmed cases varies in age,
翻译：  持久  天青月白  长颈鹿  星星与野狗
背景不同  职业也不同
background, and occupation --
一位73岁的退休教师
a 73-year-old retired schoolteacher,
一位31岁的施工起重机操作员
a 31-year-old construction crane operator,
校对：小早  杏仁斯嘉丽     中转：咖啡·Lee
一位55岁的农业设备销售员
a 55-year-old agricultural equipment salesman.
他们都来自于堪萨斯市市区
Other than they're all from the greater Kansas City metro area,
时间轴：   Avis   姜姜   壬虚浪影
此外没发现其他共同点
we haven't uncovered any other link.
还有他们都接触了蓖麻毒素
Beside the fact that they've all be exposed to ricin.
这个毒素是如何传播的
How is the toxin transmitted?
后期：虫虫不咬人    总监：小早
还没查清
It's still unclear.
国安部也查不出来吗
And DHS has no idea of a motive?
所有国安部探员都在查这件事
I've got every DHS agency working on this.
动机方面我们有所猜测  但没有确切证据
We have ideas about motives, but nothing solid, sir.
是否和艾尔萨卡有关呢
Do any of those ideas include Al-Sakar,
因为我们逮捕马吉德·纳萨尔以后他死了
in retaliation for the capture and now death of Majid Nassar?
这是可能性最大的推测
That's our most likely scenario.
很好  有情况随时告诉我
Very good. Keep me apprised of the situation.
显然我们时间非常紧迫
Obviously, time is of the essence.
谢谢各位
Thank you all.
你要当多久司机
So, how long you on carpool duty?
中情局让我返工之前
The agency's just easing me back into the job
先休息一下
till I'm back up to speed.
我想说  我拿到驾照了
Well, if it helps, I got my permit.
下次可以我开车  你坐后面
Next time I can drive, and you can ride in back.
-是吗  -对
- Yeah? - Yeah.
等你能单手组装格洛克9毫米口径手枪
When you learn to assemble a Glock 9mm with one hand,
同时以140公里时速倒车过S弯道
and drive backwards around an S-curve at 90 miles an hour,
我就让你开
I just might let you.
李奥
Leo?
-你好啊  -你认识这人吗
- Hey, buddy. - You know this guy?
我是杰拉德·阿尔伯特  来自《纪事报》
Jared Abbott. I'm with the Chronicle.
李奥  传言总统不是你的父亲
Leo, what do you think of the rumor
你对此有何看法
that the president isn't your father?
李奥  进学校去  快点
Leo, get inside the school -- now.
而你的亲生父亲是联邦在押重犯
That your real dad is actually an inmate in a federal prison?
总统的孩子们不接受采访
The president's kids are off-limits,
而且这里禁止外人入内
and you're on private property.
你再这样  我将采取武力措施
Step like that again, and I'll put you on the ground.
德鲁  把这蠢货赶出去
Drew, get this fool out of here.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
现在你成了公众人物
It's gonna happen from time to time
就会不时遇到这样的问题
now that you're in the public eye,
但你不需要对每个传言都作出回应
but it doesn't mean you got to respond to every rumor.
对吧
Right?
对
Yeah.
我去上课了
I got to get to class.
-喂  -去车里
- Hello? - Go to your car.
-然后听我们的指示  -你听着
- We'll send further instructions. - Listen to me.
让我儿子来说话  否则我不会照做
I'm not gonna do another thing until I hear from my son.
你现在没权利谈条件
You're in no position to negotiate.
我要跟我儿子说话
I want to hear my son.
卢克
Luke...
你爸找你
It's your dad.
爸爸
Daddy?
卢克
Luke.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我知道  宝贝
I know, baby.
今年你过生日我们去了哪里
Where did -- where did we go for your birthday this year?
我们去了迪士尼乐园
We went to Disney World.
对  你最喜欢的游戏是什么
Right, and what's your favorite ride?
太空任务
Mission in Space.
我很快就去接你回家
I'm gonna bring you home soon, okay?
探员  立刻去车上
Go to your car, agent -- now.
品牌广告推广合作  普罗米修斯  plmxs2016@gmail.com
认真读完
Read this.
你跟柯克曼见面
Once you're face-to-face with Kirkman,
按上面的指示行动
I want you to do exactly as it says.
我绝对不会照做
There's no way I'm doing this.
这是要求  杰森
These are the terms, Jason.
我没跟你谈条件  给你一小时
This is not a negotiation. You have an hour.
在那之后  你儿子要么能安全回家
After that, you'll either find your son safe at home...
要么不能
or not.
你应该知道你们是跑不掉的
You do know you're - not gonna get away with this?
你知道我们监视着你的一举一动
You know we're watching.
如何收场全看你的选择
It's your choice how this plays out.
国土安全部人为蓖麻毒素袭击事件
Homeland Security thinks the ricin attack
很可能是对纳萨尔的死进行的报复
is most likely retribution for Nassar's death.
如果明天要进行民意投票
The public needs to feel safe
-就必须让民众感到安全  -我知道
- if they're gonna get out and vote tomorrow. - I know.
为了保障选举顺利
We're running through a variety of situations
-我们要面临重重障碍  -亲爱的
to try and accomplish that. - Hey, sweetheart.
你怎么没在学校
Why aren't you at school?
出什么事了吗
Everything all right?
我不知道该怎么开口  但...
Um, I'm not sure how to ask this, but...
您是我的亲生父亲吗
are you my real father?
-什么  -我当然是你的父亲
- What? - Of course I'm your father.
你为什么这么问
Why would you even ask that?
在学校遇到一个记者  他这样问我的
This reporter asked me at school.
李奥  你先坐下
Leo, please sit down.
我不知道为什么那个记者
I-I-I don't understand why the reporter
会问我这个问题
would even ask me that question.
我明白这个问题一定伤害到了你
Look, I understand how hurt that must have made you feel.
拜托  李奥  你坐下  我们好好说
Please, Leo, just sit down. Let me try and --
亲爱的  听我说
Sweetheart, listen to me.
在认识你父亲之前  我曾和别人约会过
Before I met your dad, I was with someone else.
-我们分手时  我... -等等  等等
- And when we broke up, I -- - W-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
所以你也不确定到底谁才是我的亲生父亲
So -- so you don't know for sure who my dad is.
李奥  我就是你的父亲
Leo, I'm your dad.
我和你妈妈结婚了
Look, your mom and I were getting married.
她怀了你  你是我们的儿子
She was pregnant with you, our son.
我所关心的只有这些
That's all we cared about.
你们从没想过要告诉我  是吗
You guys were never gonna tell me?
李奥  没什么好跟你说的
Leo, there was nothing to tell you.
-李奥  回来  等等  -汤姆  汤姆
- Leo, come back here! Wait. - Tom, Tom, Tom.
我们现在必须说清楚
We need to talk about this now.
让他静静  汤姆  先让他静静  好吗
Give him a sec -- Tom, give him a second, okay?
我不想等到要去做亲子鉴定
I'm not waiting to take this DNA test.
发生紧急情况了吗
This better be an emergency.
疾病控制中心获得了
Sir, the CDC has new information
关于堪萨斯城的新情况
about the situation in Kansas City.
谢谢
Thank you.
蓖麻毒素事件有进展了吗
What's the update on the ricin attack?
疾控中心找到了其中的关联
CDC found the link, sir.
所有的受害者都是民意调查员
All the victims are poll workers.
民意调查员
Poll workers?
他们是明天选举的志愿者  总统先生
Volunteers, sir, for tomorrow's election.
国土安全部称蓖麻毒素被放在投票机中
Homeland Security says the ricin was deposited on the machines,
它能在空气中传播并被人们吸入
where it could become airborne and inhaled.
投毒者是要让参与投票的人被感染
Whoever did this was trying to infect people while they were voting.
而不是单纯袭击民意调查员
It's not just an isolated attack on some polls.
说的对
Damn right.
这是对整个选举的袭击
This is an attack on the election itself.
正如我希望的那样  选举要顺利召开
As much as I want - these elections to happen,
我们不能冒这个险
I don't think we can risk it.
总统先生  联调局和国安部有可能
Sir, there's still a chance the FBI and DHS
在选举前清除所有毒素
can give the all-clear before the elections.
大概有一亿四千六百万民众
It's possible as many as 146 million people
会参加明天的投票
are gonna vote tomorrow.
你们真的相信他们能彻查五十个州的
Do you honestly think that they can inspect every machine
各个投票站的全部机器吗
in every booth across all 50 states?
总统先生  我们还有一天时间
Sir, we still have a day.
酒精烟草及火器管理局找到了一些线索
ATF has several promising leads.
不  亚伦  我们只剩十七个小时了
No, Aaron. We've got 17 hours.
挽救这次选举只有十七个小时了
17 hours if we're - gonna save this election.
总统先生  我们必须再拼一把
Sir, we have to try.
你说的对
You're right.
说的没错
You're right. Okay.
联系联调局  疾控中心和国安部
Contact the FBI, CDC, and DHS.
让他们组成一个联合特遣队
Get them to form a joint task force.
马上行动
Mobilize them immediately.
他们一到  随时向我汇报
I want updates as soon as they come in.
赛斯  我要你告知媒体
Seth, I want you to tell the press
检查只是为了预防
that the inspections are precautionary
因为国家正处于警戒状态
due to the state of alert in the country.
我们还有十七个小时  伙计们
We've got 17 hours, everybody.
十七个小时  预祝我们好运
17 hours. Good luck.
明白  总统先生
Yes, sir.
赛斯  能借一步说话吗
Seth, can I borrow you for a second?
我记得你说过杰弗里·迈尔斯的事不会爆出来
I thought you said the Jeffrey Meyers story was dead.
-是的  -那你能解释一下为何有位记者
- It was. - Then can you explain to me why a reporter
跑到学校质问我的儿子
asked my son in front of his school
我是不是他的亲生父亲吗
if I was his real father?
抱歉  总统先生  我会查清楚的
I'm sorry, sir. I'll find out.
谢谢你
I would appreciate it.
-谢谢  -谢谢您
- Thank you. - Thank you.
-喂  -汉娜  我查过威德尔的案子了
- Yeah? - Hannah, I looked into the Weddle case.
我现在没空听这个
I don't have time for that right now.
-我在找亚特伍德  -先听我说完
- I'm trying to find Atwood. - Hear me out.
这案子八年前就结案了
That case was closed eight years ago.
-好吧  -威德尔曾是缉毒局的特工
- Okay. - Weddle was this DEA special agent.
他掌握了指控当地一个贩毒集团的铁证
He built an airtight case against a local cartel,
直到贩毒集团绑架了他的女儿
until the cartel kidnapped Weddle's daughter
并逼迫他销毁所有证据
and forced him to recant everything.
案子被否决了  所有的指控也被撤销了
The case was thrown out, and all charges dropped.
好的  我需要你追踪杰森的手机
Okay, I need you to track Jason's phone.
你...你...
You -- you --
要我查联调局副局长  查上司吗
A -- a deputy director of the FBI? Our boss?
听着
Listen to me.
早上那张照片里的并不是目击者
The photo you saw this morning wasn't a witness statement.
而是杀死马吉德·纳萨尔的凶手
It's the man who killed Majid Nassar.
我认为幕后凶手
I think the people who did this
正强迫杰森做一些事情  我还不确定
are trying to make Jason do something. I don't know.
但我需要知道他现在在哪
But I need to know where his is -- now.
未查询到结果
-事情有点棘手  -怎么了
- We got a problem here. - What?
亚特伍德是侦查专家
Atwood's an expert in surveillance detection.
他一定拿掉了手机电池
He must have pulled the cellphone battery.
我无法定位
I can't locate it.
好吧  黑进他汽车的导航系统
Well, hack into his in-car nav.
随便什么东西
Something, anything.
好的  等一下
Okay, give me a second
对我的专业客气点
and speak kindly about me at my trial.
找到他了
Okay. I got him.
他左转拐向了H街
He's making a left onto H Street.
-从什么地方  -24街
- From where? - 24th.
他正在左转
He's making a left.
右转
A right.
-现在往东开  -东边有什么
- Now he's heading east. - On what?
白宫
宾州
Pennsylvania.
华盛顿特区
汽车导航仪
白宫
White House.
公民会来参与投票吗
是的  由于民意调查
Yes, it is a unique election
受到了蓖麻毒素报道的威胁
that keeps getting even more unusual
使得这场独特的选举变得越来越不寻常
now that it's threatened by reports of ricin at the polls.
丽萨  有空吗
Hey, Lisa. Got a second?
什么事
Hey. What's going on?
白宫尚未
The White House has yet to...
李奥·柯克曼的报道
The Leo Kirkman story --
你不是说放弃发表这篇报道吗
I thought you said you were gonna make it go away.
-是的  -真的吗
- I did. - Really?
今天有个记者出现在李奥的学校
Some journalist showed up at Leo's school today,
出其不意地追问他
blindsided him.
我警告过你
I-I-I warned you.
就因为我不报道这件事
Just because I didn't run with the story
并不代表其他人不会调查
didn't mean someone else wasn't gonna look into this eventually.
所以那名记者是你报社的特约记者
So it's just a coincidence that that reporter
也只是个巧合吗
was some stringer from your paper?
一个叫杰拉德·阿尔伯特的年轻人
A kid named Jared Abbott.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to tell you.
我的主编就是咬着不放
My editor is a dog with a bone.
我推稿之后  他肯定是让他接手了
He must have put him on it after I bailed.
你要我去查查吗
Do you want me to look into it?
不用了  我自己查
No, it's okay. I got it from here.
我是联调局探员汉娜·威尔士
I'm Special Agent Hannah Wells.
你刚刚放行的那辆银色车
The car you just let through, the silver one --
开车人是我上司  杰森·亚特伍德
That was my boss, Jason Atwood.
我本该坐他的车的  但是我迟到了
I was supposed to be in the car with him, but I was late.
预先批准来访名单上有你的名字吗
Are you on the pre-cleared visitors list?
我说过  我迟到了
As I said to you, I was late.
我本该和他一起来的
I was supposed to be with him, so...
你应该很清楚  女士
You know better than that, ma'am.
预先批准来访名单上没有你的名字
You're either on the pre-cleared list,
-你就不能进入  -好吧
- or you're not getting in. - Okay.
杰森  我查过威德尔的案子
Jason, I looked into the Weddle case.
如果他有帮手
What happened to that DEA agent
发生缉毒局那名探员身上的事应该就能避免
could have been avoided if he had help.
让我帮你
Let me help you.
我们一起查个水落石出  拜托了
Let's figure this out together. Come on.
新语音留言
汉娜
亚特伍德局长  请进
Director Atwood. Please, come in.
-谢谢你  怀特  -总统先生
- Thank you, Wyatt. - Mr. President.
-请坐  -不用了  总统先生
- Take a seat. - I'm fine, sir.
发现纳萨尔死亡已经过了两天
It's been two days since Nassar was found dead.
我祈祷你这次来见我
I hope to God that you're coming to me
是带着答案的
with some answers this time.
我有  总统先生
I am, sir.
马吉德·纳萨尔死于一种致命剂量的毒药
Majid Nassar was killed by a lethal dose of a poison
叫做铊
called thallium.
他的食物里混入了这种毒药
It was mixed into his food.
你知道谁能接触到他的食物吗
Do we know who had access to his food?
知道  总统先生
Yes, sir.
我能
I did.
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry. What did you say?
是我在他的食物里下毒
I poisoned his food.
你说什么  局长
Excuse me, Director.
不是我听错  就是你说错了
I either misheard you or you misspoke.
不  你没听错
No, you heard me correctly.
是我下毒
I poisoned...
杀死马吉德·纳萨尔的
Majid Nassar.
这样解释不通啊
That doesn't make sense.
你为什么要这么做
Wh-- why would you do that?
在我和他谈完话之后
After speaking to him,
很明显我们永远无法获取任何情报
it was clear we wouldn't get anything, ever.
他这种人就该死
A man like that doesn't deserve to live.
我这么做是为了国会大厦所有死去的人
I did it for all those that lost their lives at the Capitol.
我这么做是为了国家  为了我的家人
I did it for my country, and I did it for my family.
我儿子
My son...
我儿子不该生活在一个
My son should not have to live in a world
容许这样的坏人存活的世界
where evil like this is allowed to exist.
我是单独行动的
I acted alone,
如果再有下次  我还会这么做  毫不犹疑
and I would do it again, no question.
等毒物报告出来
When the toxicology report comes in,
就能证实我所说的一切
it'll confirm everything that I've said.
是我杀了马吉德·纳萨尔
I killed Majid Nassar.
按下紧急按钮吧  总统先生
Press the button, sir.
总统先生  请远离办公桌
Mr. President, step away from the desk.
毒物学家刚刚完成
The toxicologist just has performed
铊中毒现场测试
this spot tests for thallium poisoning.
结果是肯定的  总统先生
It was positive, sir.
亚特伍德不可能知道那是铊
There's no way Atwood could have known it was thallium.
-除非是他下的毒  -这解释不通
- Not unless he did it. - It doesn't make sense.
整个职业生涯辛勤工作  记录毫无瑕疵
You work your entire career, build a perfect record,
晋升副局长职位
ascend to the position of deputy director,
然后就这样弃于一旦吗
and then throw it all away?
纳萨尔吹嘘自己杀了将近上千人
Nassar boasted about killing nearly a thousand people.
亚特伍德认识当中大多数人  我们都认识
Atwood knew most of them. We all did.
在911事件后
We saw people after 9/11
再心慈的人都呼喊着要血债血偿
who wouldn't hurt a fly screaming for blood.
灾难令人改变
Tragedy changes people.
这些我完全理解
I understand all that.
但感觉就是不对劲
It just doesn't feel right.
我要人去联系
I want someone to reach out
与亚特伍德最亲近的同事
to some of Atwood's closest colleagues.
调查他的心理状态
Inquire into his state of mind.
看看是否有什么我们不知道的事
See if there's something we're not being told.
我会去看看局里谁和亚特伍德最亲近
I'll see who's closest to Atwood at the bureau,
-然后安排会面  -好  去做吧
- arrange a meeting. - Okay, let's do it.
总统先生  作战指挥中心需要你去一趟
Sir, they need you in the COC.
他们在蓖麻毒素一案上发现了疑犯
They found a suspect in the ricin case.
林奇
沃尔特
前任送货司机
目前在领取残疾保险福利
沃尔特·林奇  四十四岁
Walter Lynch, 44 years of age.
以前是卡车司机
Worked as a truck driver.
最近申请了残疾保险
Currently on state disability insurance.
酒精烟草及火器管理局和联调局
ATF and FBI
在他位于斯科茨布拉夫县郊的家中逮捕了他
apprehended him at his home outside Scotts Bluff.
在他家中  我们发现了蓖麻毒素制品
In his home, we found evidence of ricin production
以及一张全国各地投票站的列表
and a list of polling stations across the country.
大多都是他以前送货的路线
Most are on his former delivery routes.
我们已经通知这些地区的警方
We've notified the authorities at these locations
-核实这些地点的安全性  -有动机吗
- to verify their safety. - Do we have a motive?
林奇在社交媒体上发布过很多
Lynch had posted multiple anti-government messages
反政府的留言
on social media.
他的观点印证了他对投票站的攻击
His attack on the polls appears to be consistent with his views.
总统先生  我认为我们应该马上发表声明
Sir, I think we should make an announcement right away.
需要让民众知道嫌疑犯已被羁押
The public should know that the suspect's in custody,
与纳萨尔没有关联
there's no link to Nassar,
去投票站是安全的
and it's safe to go to the polls.
恐怕我们现在还不能那么做  总统先生
I'm afraid we can't do that just yet, sir.
搜查林奇的网络记录显示
A search of Lynch's Web activity shows
他隶属于一个本土反政府民兵组织
he's affiliated with a domestic anti-government militia
叫做自由捍卫者
known as the Liberty Defenders.
从西部到西南部地区确认有16处投票站
16 confirmed cells throughout the West and Southwest.
自由捍卫者
林奇让其他成员在各自州的投票站
Lynch urged other members to spread ricin at polls
喷洒篦麻毒素
in their respective states.
所以威胁依然存在
So you're saying the threat is not contained.
我们的外勤探员还需要更多时间来确认
Our field officers need more time to be certain.
-还要多久  -最糟糕的情况
- How much more time? - Worst-case scenario --
需要72小时来肃清所有民兵成员
72 hours to clear all the militia members.
明天就是选举日了
The election is tomorrow.
我们无法保障
We can't say with absolute certainty
投票站绝对是安全的
that the polling stations will be safe.
总统先生  坏消息
Mr. President, I have unfortunate news.
投票站工作人员之一  明迪·赫瑟
One of the poll workers, Mindy Hesser --
-那位学校老师  -她刚刚去世了
- The schoolteacher. - She just died, sir.
谢谢各位  失陪了
Thank you, everyone. Excuse me.
杰拉德
Jared.
谢谢你能来  我是赛斯·怀特
Thanks for coming. Seth Wright.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
从未被邀请来白宫
Never been invited to the White House.
很棒吧
It's pretty cool, isn't it?
我一直梦想着来这里
I've dreamed of this place.
请坐
Have a seat.
很高兴你喜欢这里
I'm glad you like it,
因为你要是再拿总统的儿子做文章
because if you ever sandbag the President's teenage son again,
你这辈子就别想再来了
consider yourself banned for life.
淡定
Easy!
我只是做我的本职工作
I was just doing my job.
但你要是不想让我写这篇报道  那就不写
But if you want the story gone, it's gone.
-起初这篇报道都不是我的  -我知道
- It wasn't even mine to begin with. - I know.
丽萨·乔丹最后没写这篇报道
Lisa Jordan killed the story,
你的编辑就透露给你了
and then your editor slipped it onto you.
相信我  我下一个邀请的人就是他
Trust me, he's next on my invite list.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
是丽萨告诉我的  不是我的编辑
Lisa gave me the tip, not my editor.
-丽萨  -没错
- Lisa? - Yeah.
她说她自己没法写这事
She said she couldn't run with it herself,
但她觉得应该有人来写
but thought that someone should.
我知道我们一开始就不对付
Look, I know we didn't get off on the right foot,
但既然我已经来了
but since I'm already here,
你能带我看看杜鲁门建的保龄球馆吗
do you think you could show me the bowling alley Truman built?
滚出去  杰拉德
Get out of here, Jared.
无匹配
你去哪了  一直找你来着
Where have you been? I've been trying to reach you.
找到亚特伍德了吗
Find Atwood?
没有  等一下  一会儿再说
No. Hang on. We'll talk in a minute.
威尔士探员
Agent Wells.
我是亚伦·肖尔
Yes, this is Aaron Shore,
柯克曼总统的幕僚长
President Kirkman's Chief of Staff.
有什么能帮您的吗  肖尔先生
How can I help you, Mr. Shore?
你能不能来一趟白宫
I was wondering if you could stop by the White House
探讨一项高度机密的紧急事件
to discuss a highly confidential, urgent matter.
我能问事关什么吗
May I ask what this is regarding?
马吉德·纳萨尔的死
The death of Majid Nassar.
还是不能保证
No guarantees here.
我们不能再让更多无辜的生命冒险了
We can't risk any more innocent lives.
是  但难道要取消选举
Yes, sir, but canceling the election?
总统先生  没有国会  我们无法达到预算期限
Sir, without a Congress, we can't meet budget deadlines
或者提高债务上限
or raise a debt ceiling.
-经济...  -这可没有死亡人数重要
- The economy -- - Takes second place to a body count.
总统先生  即便我们推迟选举  也无法保证
Sir, even if we postpone the election, there's no guarantee
不会再有其他的威胁或者袭击
there won't be another threat or another attack.
某些时候  我们只能冒险一试
I mean, at some point, we're just gonna have to take a chance.
那要是明天有更多人在投票站去世呢
And what if more lives are lost at the polls tomorrow?
一个人就能在投票站下毒
It takes one person to poison a polling station.
上千人可能遭到感染
Thousands of people could be infected.
很抱歉  我做不到
I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
赛斯  召开发布会
Seth, gather the press.
我亲自发表声明
I'll make the announcement myself.
您的首个新闻发布会
Your first press conference.
跟我想象中不一样
Not exactly how I pictured it.
总统先生  在共和党的历史上
Sir, in the history of the Republic,
联邦选举从未被取消过
federal elections have never been canceled,
无论是因为天气  战争还是袭击威胁
not by weather, war, or threat of an attack.
不幸的是  如今就是各种开先例的时候
Well, unfortunately, we're living in a time of firsts.
让我们单独聊聊  好吗
Could I have a moment, please?
是
Sir.
结果出来了
The results came in.
李奥在等你  他想单独跟你谈谈
Leo's waiting. He wants to talk to you alone.
你看过了吗
Did you look at them?
没有
No, I didn't.
恐怕我要失去他了
I'm afraid I'm gonna lose him.
别  别说了
Don't. Stop it.
你还没有打开
You haven't opened it.
没有
No.
没有必要
I don't need to.
用不着实验室或者遗传学
I don't need a lab or genetics
来告诉我我已经知道的事
to tell me what I already know.
我一直知道的事
What I've always known,
从你诞生的那天和之后的每一天起
from the day you were born and every day since.
不管这上面的结果怎样  都改变不了什么
Whatever it says in here isn't gonna change anything.
至少对我而言不会
At least not for me.
李奥  你永远都是我儿子
Leo, you will always be my son.
我也永远是你父亲
And I will always be your father.
我之前从未跟你提起这事的唯一原因
The only reason why I never talked to you about this before,
说实话  是因为它对我不重要
honestly, is because it didn't matter to me.
但我从未想过这对你可能会有多重要
But I never thought about how it might matter to you,
这一点  是我错了
and for that, I was wrong.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
这份结果
So, this...
是给你的  无论你打开与否
is for you, to open or not.
检测者编号
不管你怎么选择  我都会尊重
And whatever you chose to do, I will respect.
但是  李奥  我希望你知道我有多爱你
But, Leo, I need you to know how much I love you.
我该去继续做作业了
I should finish my homework.
好
Yeah.
要不然你们准备如何应对恐怖分子
How else do you plan to stand up to terrorists?
推迟选举  直到选民能安全投票
Wouldn't it be better to postpone the election
不是更好一些吗
until the polls can be properly secured?
这样就不必用选举工作人员
That way, we're not risking the lives
以及选民的生命冒险
of the poll workers and the voters.
现在让我们直播连线
We're now getting word we're going to go live now
首位蓖麻毒素受害者
to the woman whose mother, Mindy Hesser,
明迪·赫瑟的女儿
was the first victim of the ricin poisoning.
我母亲在选举站做义工
My mother volunteered at the polls
因为她觉得每个人都有发言权
because she thought everyone deserved to have a voice.
民众为选举日恐怖袭击担忧
她说已经有很多人为这理想献出了生命
She said so many people sacrificed their lives for that ideal.
她至少能尽一份力  帮助大选顺利进行
The least she could do was help elections run smoothly.
明迪·赫瑟
蓖麻毒素受害者
她就是这样的人
That's the kind of person she was.
我希望能有更多的人像她一样
I wish more of us were like her.
抱歉
Sorry.
再等几分钟就能开始了
Should just be a couple more minutes.
你四十五分钟前就是这么说的
That's what you said 45 minutes ago.
没错  娜塔莉  如果他四十五分钟后
Yes, Natalie. I'll say it again in another 45
还没到的话  我还会这么说
if he's not here.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎美国总统
the president of the United States.
-谢谢  赛斯  -谢谢  总统先生
- Thank you, Seth. - Thank you, sir.
大家请坐
Please, be seated.
-大家下午好  -下午好
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
如大家所知
As you already know,
我们在堪萨斯城的一些投票站
some of our polling stations in the Kansas City area
遭受了生物恐怖袭击
have been the subject of a bioterrorism attack.
虽然联邦政府  州政府和当地支付机构
And even though our federal, state, and local law officials
都向我们保证投票站是安全的
are assuring us that the polling stations will be safe,
很多美国人民依然担惊受怕  这很正常
understandably, many Americans are still scared.
遗憾的是  我们的一名选举站志愿者
Tragically, one of our volunteer poll workers
在这次袭击中丧失了生命
lost their life during the attack.
她的名字是明迪·赫瑟
Her name was Mindy Hesser.
有很多选举志愿工作者都拒绝
And as many of our poll workers have declined
参与这次的选举工作
to volunteer this election cycle
因为他们害怕还会有袭击  但明迪站出来了
for fear of further attacks, Mindy showed up.
她布置好桌子  更新好投票机
She set up her table, updated her voting rolls,
将近二十三年里  她一直如此
as she has for nearly 23 years.
就在刚刚  我有幸和明迪的女儿通了话
Moments ago, I had the honor of talking to Mindy's daughter,
她告诉我任何的恐慌或者畏惧
and she told me that no fear or uncertainty
都不能阻止她的母亲
would ever have prevented her mother
执行她认为最重要的
from carrying out what she considered
公民义务
to be her most important civic duty --
保护我们的选举权利
protecting our right to vote.
我的很多同事
Many of my colleagues
都建议我取消本次选举
have advised me to cancel these elections.
但是我受到了明迪的行动的启发
But I have been inspired by Mindy's actions.
所以我决定
So I have decided that these elections
本次选举将会按计划进行
will go forward as planned.
明早我自己也会和美国同胞一样
Tomorrow morning, I myself will go to the polls
去选举站  投出我的一票
alongside my fellow Americans, and I will cast my ballot.
我相信这是我们应该感谢明迪以及每一位
I believe we owe it to Mindy and to every other American
为保护民主政治而付出生命的美国人
that has given their life to protect our great democracy.
我们不能生活在恐惧中
We cannot live in fear.
我们也不会生活在恐惧中
We will not live in fear.
谢谢  天佑美国
Thank you, and God bless America.
恭喜你  先生
Congratulations, sir.
大选将会按照计划进行
I understand the election will go on as planned.
-这么做是对的  先生  -谢谢
- It was the right move, sir. - Thank you.
不幸的是  这不是我叫你们来的原因
Unfortunately, that is not why I asked you both here.
今天早上十点左右
Earlier today, at approximately 10:00 A.M.,
杰森·亚特伍德承认他杀了马吉德·纳萨尔
Jason Atwood confessed to the killing of Majid Nassar.
等等  我没理解  联调局的副局长
Wait, I'm sorry. The deputy director of the FBI
杀死了世界上的头号恐怖分子吗
killed the world's most wanted terrorist?
恐怕是这样的
I'm afraid so.
在他向我供认的时候
During his confession to me,
他说他认为
he stated that he did not believe
纳萨尔不会向我们
that Nassar was gonna provide us
提供任何有用的信息
with any useful information
他为了在国会大厦惨案中牺牲的同胞
and that on behalf of our fallen at the Capitol Building,
出于爱国职责  他杀死了纳萨尔
he felt it his patriotic duty to take Nassar's life.
出于他的爱国职责吗
His patriotic duty?
这是谋杀  也是国家安全的严重失败
It's murder, and a catastrophic failure of national security.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
我非常想充分调查这个案件
And I have every intention of investigating it,
但现在这个案子是高度机密
but right now, the case is strictly classified
仅有军队最高司令官及联调局有管辖权
and under the jurisdiction of Army CIC and the FBI.
我已经让亚伦·肖尔
I have asked Aaron Shore
去审问一些亚特伍德的好友同事
to interview some of Atwood's closest colleagues.
希望我们能找出更多的线索
Hopefully we can find out something more.
明天的选举能够组建国会
Well, tomorrow's election gives us a Congress.
然后我可以展开独立调查来协助你
Then I can open up an independent investigation to assist you.
我不确定我们新国会的首次行动
I'm not sure if the first act of our new Congress
是这次调查
should be this investigation.
无疑还有更紧要的事情
Surely there are more pressing issues
需要我们展开
that we need to get on with.
不  彼得  我觉得议员是对的
No, Peter, I think the congresswoman is right.
我们最先要做的应该是赢得国家的信任
Our first priority should be gaining the nation's trust.
金布尔  谢谢你
Kimble, thank you.
赛斯
Seth?
总统刚刚的演讲很棒
Great speech by the president.
你润色加工过了  对吧
You did a final polish, right?
我们做好了约定  但你却没有信守承诺
You know, we had a deal, and you broke it.
揭穿水门事件丑闻的记者之一
下次你再想当伍德沃那样的记者的话
Next time you try to be a Woodward,
披露该丑闻的另一名记者
挑伯恩斯坦做搭档  别挑杰拉德·阿尔伯特
pick a better Bernstein than Jared Abbott.
公平来讲  我只是说
Look, to be fair, all I said
我不会报道那件事  而我也没有报道
was that I wouldn't run with the story, and I didn't.
是的  你只是把它给了别人
No, you just gave it to somebody else.
赛斯  拜托
Seth, come on.
无论你喜欢与否  那是新闻
Like it or not, it is news.
也许对你来说不是  但对于明天即将投票的
Maybe not to you, but to millions of Americans
数百万美国人来说
about to cast their votes tomorrow,
总统对待真相的态度是很重要的
the president's relationship with the truth means something.
我喜欢你
I like you.
赛斯  我真的很喜欢你
Seth, I really do.
好吗  但如果让我在你和真相之间选择的话
Okay? But asking me to choose between you and the truth
我们两个都不会高兴看到那样的结果
will produce an outcome that won't make either of us happy.
未知号码
不要告诉肖尔先生任何事
谢谢你能在短时间内前来
Thank you for coming in on such short notice.
有什么我能帮你的吗
How can I help you?
这话很难开口
There's no easy way to say this,
但是今天早些
but earlier today,
亚特伍德局长见过总统
Director Atwood met with the president,
而且他承认杀死了马吉德·纳萨尔
and he confessed - to assassinating Majid Nassar.
他宣称自己使用铊
Now, he claims to have used thallium...
-不会的  -毒杀了纳萨尔
- No. - to poison Nassar.
不可能
That's not possible.
所有人都很震惊
This is a shock to everyone,
所以我想找你谈谈
which is why I wanted to speak with you
确认你是否有发现任何疑点
to see if you've noticed anything out of the ordinary,
近期生活有变之类的
recent life changes.
他有说过一些奇怪的话吗
Has he said anything unusual?
过去一周内有任何可疑之处吗
Anything suspicious in the past week?
威尔士探员
Agent Wells?
-抱歉  -我知道这一时难以接受
- Sorry. I... - I can understand this is overwhelming,
但你能想起任何可以帮我们
but can you think of anything
理清亚特伍德谋杀纳萨尔一案的事情吗
that might help us understand Atwood's murder of Nassar?
没有
No.
-我可以见他吗  -抱歉  威尔士探员
- May I see him? - I'm sorry, Agent Wells,
他被关押在高度设防的监狱内
but he is being held in a maximum-security facility.
不允许探视
He's not allowed any visitors.
恰克  你能追踪到那条短信吗
Chuck, tell me you can trace that text.
全球情报机构里
You know, there's only a handful of people
只有少数几个人
in the global intelligence community
懂得如何追踪短信
capable of tracing a text.
-你是其中之一吗  -不
- And you're one of them, right? - No.
路由追踪汉娜·威尔士的手机网络
开始使用摩萨德密钥追踪
幸亏我认识摩萨德[以色列情报机构]的人
But luckily, I know someone with the Mossad
他给了我密钥
who passed me an encryption key.
你能查到发送地址吗
So you can get a location?
没那么简单
It's not that easy.
追踪完成
我只查到了对方号码  你将就一下吧
Instead, you'll have to settle for a phone number.
总统冒生命危险投票
为了鼓励民众投票
In a bid to encourage voter turnout,
柯克曼总统明天将亲自去投票站投票
President Kirkman will cast his vote at the polls tomorrow.
特勤局会让他去吗
Secret Service is gonna let him go?
你们不是要保护他的吗
Thought you guys were supposed to protect him.
柯克曼总统实在太天真
President Kirkman being naive
竟然会认为美国人民...
to think the American people...
当父母的总有自己的想法
Parents get their own ideas.
投票箱...
ballot box...
正当举国上下为投票日准备之时
As the country prepares for election day,
似乎大家都有一个疑问...
the question that seems to be on everyone's mind...
自从我加入特勤局后
You know, my... my dad's called me every day
我父亲每天都会给我打电话
since I joined the Secret Service
确认我是否安全
just to make sure I'm staying safe.
迈克  我...
Mike, I...
我知道你想说什么
I know what you're doing.
你想说  无论怎样  我爸爸都会在乎我
You're trying to tell me, no matter what, my dad cares.
不  我只想和你说说我的父亲
No, I'm telling you about my dad.
他教我扣篮  还教我怎么和女生搭话
Taught me how to hoop and how to talk to girls.
没有他  就没有今天的我
He pretty much made me who I am today.
可有趣的是  我三岁时才认识他
The funny thing is, I didn't know him till I was 3.
也就是我母亲嫁给他的时候
That's when my mom married him.
我从未见过我的生父
I never met my biological father.
那些鉴定只代表生理学上的结果
Those tests... They tell you biology.
而并不能决定你真正的父亲是谁
But they don't tell you who your dad is.
别看新闻看得太晚
Don't stay up too late watching the news.
眼见不一定为实
Can't always trust what you see.
在恐怖主义威胁之下投票率成谜
今天是2月7日  星期三
It's Wednesday, February 7th,
总统及全国民众翘首以盼的日子
the day the president and our nation have been waiting for.
东部时间早上6点半开始
Beginning at 6:30 a.m. in the East,
全国各地的投票站将陆续开门
polls across the country will be open.
大家都在怀疑
The question, of course, on everyone's mind
会有选民出现吗
are voters going to show up?
当地警方  消防部门
Local police and fire departments,
-还有国民警卫队...  -你很美
- even the National Guard... - You look beautiful.
均已进驻全国各地的投票站
have been stationed at polling stations across the country.
你和李奥谈过了吗
Have you spoken to Leo?
没  还没有
No, not a word.
我不知道他看了鉴定结果没有
I don't even know if he's opened the test results yet.
-你呢  -我也没
- You? - No.
他也不肯和我说话
He won't speak to me either.
当我在宣读就职誓言时
When I was taking the oath of office,
我唯一真正害怕的事情是
you know, the only thing I was honestly scared about
这将会如何影响我的家庭
was what this could possibly do to our family.
但我没料到会出现这种情况
I could never have seen this one coming.
无论他的决定是什么
Well, whatever he decides,
我们都必须承认现在的家已容不下半点秘密
we've realized our new house can't hold any secrets.
没错
Yeah.
安全
Clear.
投票点
也许稍后情况会好转
Maybe it'll pick up later.
要来赌一把吗
Yeah, you want to put money on that?
很抱歉  亲爱的
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
汤姆
Tom...
我了解这幅神情
I know that look.
来吧  和我说说
Come on, talk to me.
我发誓要尽我所能
I took a vow to do everything in my power
使美国在爆炸案后重新振作起来
to lead this country back after the bombing.
我知道我们已经解决了很多难题
I know we've had a few things thrown at us,
但若我连鼓励国民投票这事也办不成...
but if I can't even get the American people to vote...
当大多数人都选择逃避之时
You made a decision to move forward with the elections
是你决定继续进行投票
when most would have shied away.
你做出了国家所需的承诺
You made a commitment that this country needed,
所以我们终于有国会了
and now we're finally gonna have a Congress.
这样的国会算得上什么
What kind of a Congress is that gonna be?
仅代表十分之一国民的议会
A House that represents 10% of the country
根本不能被称为政府部门
is no government at all.
他们认为我出任总统并不合法
They call me an illegitimate president.
也将认为此国会违法  而且他们并没有错
They'll call it an illegitimate Congress, and they'd be right.
汤姆  他们看到你去投票了
Tom, they saw you go to the polls.
他们知道可以相信你
They know that they can trust you.
他们不是说了  每一张选票都很重要吗
Don't they say that one vote can make all the difference?
你也在场
You were there, also.
-那里只有两位选民  -是的
- That's two votes. - Yeah.
希望他们投的不是对立票
Let's hope they don't cancel each other out.
李奥  你还好吗
Leo, everything all right?
我昨晚睡不着
I couldn't sleep last night.
我不希望把这份结果放在我房间
I don't want this in my room.
你还没打开
It's still sealed.
我也不需要打开它
I don't need to open it either.
我知道你是我爸爸
I know you're my dad.
快过来
Come... Come here.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他肯定是我的儿子
He's definitely my son.
这不好笑
That's not even funny.
先生  他们在等你
Sir? They're waiting for you.
抱歉  怎么了
I'm sorry. What is it?
亚伦  等我一下  马上就去
Aaron, give me a second. I'll be right in.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
这是美国历史上不寻常的选举
It's an unusual election in American history.
堪萨斯市的蓖麻毒素袭击
The ricin attack in Kansas City
让整个国建陷入震惊
has sent shock waves throughout the country.
借过  谢谢
Excuse me. Thank you.
很多选民害怕投票
Many voters are afraid to vote.
虽然投票现场很有可能门可罗雀
But what was threatening to be a light turnout
国会特殊选举
选举日
却完全不然
is not so light after all.
选民在选举站排起长队
Voters are lining up at the polling booths
全国投票开始  选民投票率颇高
确保自己的投票算数
to make sure their votes are counted.
当问及他们今天为什么决定来
When asked why they decided to come out today,
全国投票开始  选民投票率颇高
大多数人表示
the majority said,
"因为柯克曼总统去投票了"
"Because President Kirkman went to vote."
他们投票了  总统先生
They're voting, Mr. President.
选票晚些时候才能统计完全
They won't have complete returns until later,
但他们称其为民主的胜利
but they're already calling it a victory -- for democracy.
谢谢  赛斯
Thank you, Seth.
还有国土安全局的通知
Also, got a heads-up from DHS.
联合行动组检查了
The joint task force followed through
剩下的民兵队员
with the remaining militia members.
他们认为没有蓖麻毒素了
They concluded there's no more ricin.
林奇是单独行动的
Lynch was acting alone.
明天你就有个国会了
Tomorrow, you'll have a Congress.
新政府
A new government.
我们还需要内阁和副总统
We'll still need a Cabinet and a vice president,
但我们还在努力
but we're working on it.
亚伦  我们会成功的
We'll get there, Aaron.
投票选民破历史记录
有亚特伍德的消息吗
Any word on Atwood?
我跟威尔士探员谈过了
I spoke to Agent Wells.
她说的话不能消除他的供述
She said nothing to dispel his confessions.
好的
Okay.
赛斯
Seth?
有件事要你帮我
There's something I need you to do for me.
总统先生  这位是丽萨·乔丹
Mr. President, Lisa Jordan.
我知道你一直对我和我的儿子有疑问
I know you've been asking questions about me and my son.
我给你答案
I have your answer.
确切的回答
A definitive one.
DNA鉴定
A DNA test.
误差万分之一
Margin of error -- .01%.
基本确凿无疑
About as certain as you're gonna find in this world.
我是李奥的生父
I am Leo's biological father.
我觉得这不再是什么新闻了
I can't imagine it's much of a story anymore,
但我想让你知道真相
but I wanted you to know the truth.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
丽萨·乔丹  媒体
我应该把这个还给我的编辑
I assume I should hand these back to my editor.
不用为了我这样
Not on my account.
我相信记者强则国强
I believe our country is only as strong as our journalists.
我希望你敦促我们保持诚实
I expect you to keep us honest.
乔丹女士
Ms. Jordan.
谢谢  赛斯
Thank you, Seth.
晚安  先生
Good night, sir.
看来我们还要共事
So I guess we'll still be working together.
对  但仅仅是共事了
Yes, but only working.
我相信过你
I trusted you.
而你却利用了我的信任
You took advantage of it.
谢谢你  新闻发言人先生
Thank you, Mr. Press Secretary.
谢谢你  乔丹女士
Thank you, Ms. Jordan.
喂
Hello?
上次我们交谈时  我发现了105室
Last time we spoke, I found Room 105,
而现在我唯一相信的人锒铛入狱
and now the only person I trust is behind bars.
你怎么知道这个号码的
How did you get this number?
我不想跟一个匿名者打电话
I'm done talking to an anonymous voice over the phone.
你有话说  就来见我
You have something to say to me, meet me.
晚上11点14分
11:14 p.m.
哪里
Where?
我从没打算见你
I don't intend to meet you, ever.
晚上11点14分
11:14 p.m.
-去查  -等等
- Look into it. - Wait.
你真是一脸得意
Don't you look happy.
是好日子
Well, it's a good day.
总统得到了他的国会
The president is getting his Congress...
这就是我来的原因
which is why I'm here.
我想让你知道
I wanted to let you know
如果你要调查
that if you do go ahead with an investigation,
我不会支持你
it will be without my support.
彼得  我敬佩你的忠诚
I admire your loyalty, Peter.
我只是不明白
I just don't understand it.
我们都知道柯克曼会坑了他自己
We both know Kirkman can't get out of his own way.
是因为他缺乏经验
Whether it's his lack of experience
或是眼下时局
or the times we're in...
他这个总统都长不了
he won't last.
除非这就是你的如意算盘
Unless that's what you're counting on --
当他下台的时候  假设你当了副总统
that when he goes down, assuming you make it to V.P.,
你就是笑到最后的人
you would be the last man standing.
这是通往白宫的康庄大道
It's a brilliant path to the White House.
我不敢相信我到现在才发现
I just can't believe I didn't see it until now.
你的想象力真是太过丰富了  金布尔
You got an overactive imagination, Kimble.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
但当我扳倒他时
But when I take him down,
我保证我也不会放过你的
I'll make sure I don't leave you behind.
晚安  金布尔
Good night, Kimble.
你迟到了
You're late.
亚特伍德今天替我们收拾了残局
Atwood managed to tie up a loose end for us today.
我听说了
I heard.
你要控制任何的附带后果
I want you to stay on top of any fallout,
任何涉及纳萨尔死因的调查
any further investigation into Nassar's murder.
好
Fine.
开心点  彼得
Cheer up, Peter.
你只有一步之遥了
You're about to be a heartbeat away.
在那发生前
And how many more good people
还要摧毁多少好人
need to be destroyed before that happens?
就一个
Just one.
打开微信
扫描左侧二维码
关注凤凰八卦
■